Guide to the Charlotte Beers papers, 1958-2013 and undated RL.11767
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1992-2013 and undated; 7
  - Charlotte and Cheryl--Editorial consultation track 2-3, 2007 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-021)
  - Charlotte and Cheryl--Editorial consultation part 2 copy, 2007 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-022)
  - Charlotte and Cheryl--MP3 files, 2007 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-023)
  - Charlotte and Martha--Indiana Governor's Conference, 2013 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-024)
  - Charlotte Beers opening keynote speech, 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-025)
  - Charlotte's book files, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-026)
  - CMA 2005--Chief Marketing Officers' speech (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-027)
  - David Ogilvy: The Original Mad Man 59:00 BBC version, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-028)
  - Department of Defense--Ad Council presentation, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-029)
  - Examples of Public Diplomacy Initiatives 2002-2003, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-030)
  - Family for Xmas, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-031)
  - Fortune Conferences, Most Powerful Women in Business: Charlotte Beers, 30:00, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-032)
  - Fortune Conferences, Most Powerful Women in Business: Charlotte Beers, 30:00, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-033)
  - Good Morning America; Harvard cuts, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-034)
  - Good Morning America; Harvard cuts, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-035)
  - Harvard Business School interview, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-036)
  - Harvard Business School interview, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-037)
  - Harvard Business School interview, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-038)
  - Harvard Business School interview, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-039)
  - J. Walter Thompson--Black History Month, 2009 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-040)
  - Jaguar, American Express, IBM spots, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-041)
  - Jaguar, American Express, IBM spots, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-042)
  - Jaguar spots, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-043)
  - Laurel Photos, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-044)
  - Madonna--What It Feels Like for a Girl, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-045)
  - Meet the Press, 2002 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-046)
  - Morning Joe Show, 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-047)
  - Morning Joe Show, 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-048)
  - Miss Representation (OWN Documentary Club), 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-049)
  - Muslim Life Magazine, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-050)
  - National Press Club--Mix, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-051)
  - National Press Club--News Conference, 2002 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-052)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--A Case Study of Brand at American Express, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-053)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Brandprint, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-054)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Charlotte Beers/Harvard, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-055)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Charlotte Beers/Harvard, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-056)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Charlotte Beers/Harvard, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-057)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Charlotte Beers/Harvard, 1994 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-058)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Jaguar, Dove Brandprint, 1995 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-059)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--Harvard Business Publishing, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-060)
  - Ogilvy & Mather--IBM spots, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-061)
    Includes: Nuns; Bangkok; French Guys
  - Reality of Mad Men--Hartman Center/AAF-RDU talk at Duke University, 2008 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-062)
  - Reality of Mad Men--Hartman Center/AAF-RDU talk at Duke University, 2008 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-063)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee--American Public Diplomacy and Islam, 2003 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-064)
  - Shared Values Initiative, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-065)
  - SMU base presentation, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-066)
  - SMU visuals, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-067)
  - SMU visuals in Powerpoint, 2002 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-068)
  - Tatham RSCG--Happy Trails Charlotte, 1992 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-069)
  - Tatham RSCG--Happy Trails Charlotte edited, 1992 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-070)
  - Tavis Smiley Show, 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-071)
  - Tavis Smiley Show, 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-072)
  - TedX Women--The Space Between/Charlotte Beers, 2012 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-073)
  - Telecon w/Cheryl Woodruff, 2008 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-074)
  - This Week with Cookie Roberts, Meet the Press, 2002 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-075)
  - United Way, Washington DC speech, 2004 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-076)
  - USAID--Public Diplomacy and Foreign Aid, 2003 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-077)
  - U.S. Department of State--Miscellaneous data, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-078)
  - U.S. Department of State--Miscellaneous data, 2001 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-079)
    Includes: Network of Terrorism; Defeating Terrorism, Defending Freedom; Muslim Life in America
  - U.S. Department of State--Miscellaneous data, 2001 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-080)
  - Video from National Press Corps presentation, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-081)
  - Voice of America TV--Aids in Africa: A fight for survival, undated (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-082)
  - Voice of America/Arab TV--60 Minutes, CBS Evening News, Al-Hurr TV, 2004 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-083)
  - Women's Forum, remarks by Beers, 2nd copy, 32:00, 2002 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-092)
  - WPP: Integrating Icons to Leverage Knowledge, Joseph Bower, 44:18, 2002 (Box AV2, Video-disc RL11767-OP-093)